

MD.SHAMIM MIA Sr. Executive - Sales

Contact

Ka-147/2/B, (03rd Floor) (C3) Nayanagar, Khilkhat, Dhaka-1229.

Mobile: 01719-396618

Email: shamimmimky@gmail.com
LinkedIn:linkedin.com/in/md-

shamim-mia-7aa8b197

Education

MBA (Masters of Business Administration)

Result - B+ (3.27 out of 4) (2015 - 2016) Accounting & Information Systems Jagannath University, Dhaka.

MSS (Masters of Social Science), Economics

Result - 01st Class (62% Marks) (2013 - 2015) Govt. Titumir College National University, Dhaka.

BSS (Bachelor of Social Science), Economics

Result – 02nd Class (56% Marks) (2007-2013) Govt. Titumir College National University, Dhaka.

HSC (Higher Secondary Certificate)

Science, Result - 3.70 out of 5 (2004 - 2006) G B G College, Ghatail, Tangail.

SSC (Secondary School Certificate) Science, Result - 3.25 out of 5 (2002 - 2003) Ghatail Gono Pilot High School, Ghatail, Tangail.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Performance marketer, passionate about KPIs and growing customer base, and fully equipped with good knowledge of sales strategies and techniques, as well as exceptional ability to prepare sales demonstrations for team building and increased revenue.

Work Experience

Runner Automobiles Ltd.

Senior Executive-Sales Division October '19 to Present

Key Responsibilities:

Responsible for achieve Sales and Collection target of the assigned Show Room, Customer Service planning, organizing the corporate strategy and implementing it through the team mates with a view to achieve the COCO Show Room's Monthly and Yearly sales and collection target so that the company will be able to reach it's desired objectives.

Key Achievement:

• Achieved a 125% sales target upon last quarter of 2019 and maintained it still now.

Greenland Services Ltd (Herfy)

Restaurant Manager (Acting Area Manager) May 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 5 months)

Key Responsibilities:

As above store leader this is my responsibility to keep continue the popularity of Herfy Bangladesh. Analysis Store Cost of Sale, Profit & Lose, Management Training, Team Training, Local Marketing, Product Quality etc.

Key Achievement:

• Achieved 5% COS (Cost of Sale) minimize of each branches and open new outlet with giving proper guideline as per standard.

Transcom Foods Limited

Restaurant General Manager October 2009 - May 2018 (08 years 09 months)

Key Responsibilities:

As a Head of the branch, I am the responsible for all the activities. Customer Satisfaction, Team Handling, Team Satisfaction, Team Motivation, Store Training, Cash Management, Inventory Management, Operation monitoring day to day, Local Marketing etc which is all for my responsibility.

Key Achievement:

- Achieved Beating year ago sales-2019, Best Presenter-2016 and Best Restaurant Award-2015.
- Successfully open four outlets.
- Best Punctual Employee 2010, Earned multiple "Employee of the Month" awards & Great Inventory Counting as a Team.

SKILLS

- Good Communications Skill
- Sales & Marketing
- Time Management
- Negotiation Skill
- Supervision & Management Skill
- Strong Work Ethic
- Proven Leadership Skill
- Ability to Motivate.

Hobbies

- Travel
- Team Sports (Cricket)
- Listining Music etc.

Biography

Father's Name: Md. Amej Uddin Mother's Name: Amina Begum

Date of Birth: 01st Jan'1988

Marital+ Status: Married
Place of Birth: Jamalpur
Nationality: Bangladeshi

Religion: Islam

Reference

Md. Nurnobi Alam

Associate Professor (Economics)

Tongi Govt. College Contact: 01711-443752 Email: alamzip@yahoo.com

M Mainuddin Mainul Country Head

Good Neighbors Bangladesh Contact: 01712-587380

Email: maeen@gnbangla.org

Certifications

> PGDSCM

Topic: Supply Chain Management

Institute: BIMS

Duration: 06 Month (2018).

> English & Business Communication

Topic: English Skill & Business Communication Development

Institute: BITM

Duration: 01 Month (2017-18).

➤ Lead A Shift (LAS) & Lead A Restaurant (LAR)

Topic: Cash Management, Team Handling, HR, Inventory, Customer Satisfaction etc.

Institute: Transcom Foods Limited

Duration: 01 Month Each Training (2014 & 2015).

> Ujjibok Training

Topic: Leadership Skills

Institute: The Hunger project- Bangladesh

Duration: 07th, 08th & 9th Feb'2005.

Volunteer Experience

Organization : Youth Ending Hunger

Role: Leadership Program

Description: Self-Motivation, Social Responsibility, Leadership

Activities, Program organize, Presentation Skill etc.

Duration: 05 Years (Jan'2003 to Dec'2007).

Computer Skills

- ➤ Word processing package: MS-Word, MS-Excel, MS-PowerPoint.
- ➤ Basic Hardware, Browsing & E-mail

Language

- Bangla
- English

Md. Shamim Mia

Date:

